They risked everything to uncover the truth.
Shock and Awe is a history, drama, thriller film directed by Rob Reiner.
A group of journalists covering George Bush's planned invasion of Iraq in 2003 are skeptical
of the presidents claim that Saddam Hussein has "weapons of mass destruction."
Warren Strobel, played by James Marsden.
Jonathan Landay, played by Woody Harrelson.
John Walcott, played by Rob Reiner.
Lisa Mayr, played by Jessica Biel.
Vlatka Landay, played by Milla Jovovich.
Joe Galloway, played by Tommy Lee Jones.
Shock and Awe is a 2017 American drama film starring and
directed by Rob Reiner and written by Joey Hartstone.
The film also stars Woody Harrelson, Tommy Lee Jones, James Marsden, Milla Jovovich, and Jessica Biel, and follows a group of journalists at
Knight Ridder's Washington Bureau who investigate the rationale behind the Bush Administration's then-impending 2003 invasion of Iraq.
The film had its world premiere at the Zurich Film
Festival on September 30, 2017.
It was released through DirecTV Cinema on June 14, 2018, before having a limited
release in theaters on July 13, 2018, by Vertical Entertainment.
The film explores themes of journalist, iraq war, 9/11, usa politics.
The tone is emotional and intense.